export const data1=[
    {
        id:1,
        question:"What is a data Structure?",
        option1:"A programming language",
        option2:"A collection of algorithms",
        option3:"A way to store and organize data",
        option4:"A type of computer hardware",
        ans:"3",
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:"What are the disadvantages of arrays?",
        option1:"Index value of an array can be negative",
        option2:"Elements are sequentially accessed",
        option3:"Data structure like queue or stack cannot be implemented",
        option4:"There are chances of wastage of memory space if elements inserted in an array are lesser than the allocated size",
        ans:"4",
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question:"Which data structure is used for implementing recursion?",
        option1:"Stack",
        option2:"Queue",
        option3:"List",
        option4:"Array",
        ans:"1",
    },
    {
        id:4,
        question:"The data structure required to check whether an expression contains a balanced parenthesis is?",
        option1:"Queue",
        option2:"Stack",
        option3:"Tree",
        option4:"Array",
        ans:"2",
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question:"Which of the following is not the application of stack?",
        option1:"1. Data Transfer between two asynchronous process",
        option2:"Compiler Syntax Analyzer",
        option3:"Tracking of local variables at run time",
        option4:"4. A parentheses balancing program",
        ans:"1",
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question:"What is a data structure?",
        option1:"A programming language",
        option2:"A collection of algorithms",
        option3:"A way to store and organize data",
        option4:"A type of computer hardware",
        ans:"2",
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:"What is a data structure?",
        option1:"A programming language",
        option2:"A collection of algorithms",
        option3:"A way to store and organize data",
        option4:"A type of computer hardware",
        ans:"1",
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:"What is a data structure?",
        option1:"A programming language",
        option2:"A collection of algorithms",
        option3:"A way to store and organize data",
        option4:"A type of computer hardware",
        ans:"1",
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:"What is a data structure?",
        option1:"A programming language",
        option2:"A collection of algorithms",
        option3:"A way to store and organize data",
        option4:"A type of computer hardware",
        ans:"4",
    },
    {
        id:10,
        question:"What is a data structure?",
        option1:"A programming language",
        option2:"A collection of algorithms",
        option3:"A way to store and organize data",
        option4:"A type of computer hardware",
        ans:"3",
    },
]